【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
前情提要
Previously on Friends
劳驾 小姐                   菲比耶
Excuse me, Miss.         It's Phoebe.
就这些吗
Okay, will that be all?
她们是双胞胎
They're twins.
菲比是菲比 乌苏拉却很辣
Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot.
这是送给乌苏拉的
It's for Ursula.
当然 好 合适
Sure, yeah. Okay,fits.
马塞尔 把遥控器还给罗斯
Marcel, give Rossy the remote.
他怎么办到的
How did he do this?
还不全是因为乌苏拉
It's this whole stupid Ursula thing.
他是在跟她约会
So he's going out with her.
我是说 真有这么糟糕吗
I mean,is it really so terrible?
你不了解我姐姐
You don't know my sister.
你得找乔伊谈谈
You've gotta talk to Joey.
他爱上了她了
He's falling in love with her.
你不会失去他的
You aren't gonna lose him.
他们连床都没上
They haven't even slept together yet.
这不算什么
I mean, that's not serious.
有事吗
Yeah, may we help you?
瑞秋 瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel!
我没事    我没事
I'm okay！ I'm okay！
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第17集
双胞胎(下)The One With Two Parts
调校制作：寒 枫     字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
我的室友拆圣诞灯的时候
Hi, my friend here was taking down our Christmas lights
跌下了阳台
and she fell off the balcony
可能伤到脚或是脚踝或是哪儿了
and may have broken her foot or ankle or something.
天啊 你们家的圣诞灯到现在还亮着
My God, you still have your Christmas lights up?
填好后交给我
Fill this out, bring it back to me
来吧
Okay. Here you go.
好了
All right.
名字
Name...
地址
Address...
紧急联络人
Okay. In case of emergency, call...?
你
You.
真的
Really?
对
Yeah.
你真好
Oh, that is so sweet.
当然啦
Sure!
我爱你
Oh, gosh. I love you.
保险
Okay, insurance?
打勾 当然需要保险
Oh, yeah. check it. Definitely, I want some of that.
你没有保险
You don't have insurance?
为什么要有 这要花多少钱啊
Why? How much is this gonna cost?
我不知道
I have no idea.
单照X光就可能要几百块
But Xrays alone could be a couple hundred dollars.
那要怎么办
What are we gonna do?
没有太多办法可想
There's not much we can do.
除非我用你的
Unless, unless I use yours.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
等等
Well, now, wait a second.
我刚才紧急联络人填的是谁
Who did I just put as my "incase of emergency" person?
这是保险欺诈
That's insurance fraud.
好吧 那就算了
Well, all right, then. Forget it.
那回家好了
Might as well just go home.
好吧 过来 讨厌
Okay, okay, come here. I hate this.
谢啦 谢啦 我爱你
Thank you. Thank you. I love you.
给我一份新表格
Hi, heh. Urn, I'm gonna need a new set of these forms.
为什么
Why?
我简直就是个笨蛋
I'm really an idiot
我帮我朋友填表格
You see I was filling out my friend's form
填的不是她的资料
and instead of putting her information
填成我自己的
I put mine.
你的确是个笨蛋
You are an idiot.
没错 这就是我 我就是这么笨
Yep, that's me. I am that stupid.
昨天晚上我做了一个梦
I had a dream last night
我梦到跟儿子打橄榄球
where I was playing football with my kid.
很温馨
That's nice!
很好
Nice!
不 是把他当成球
No,no, with him.
我人在球场上 他们把小孩丢给我
I'm on this field, and they hike me the baby.
我必须得做点什么
I know l've gotta do something
因为坦帕湾队的防守球员逐渐向我逼近
because the Tampa Bay defense is coming right at me.
坦帕湾队很差
Tampa Bay's got a terrible team.
是没错 但
Right, but...
只有我和我儿子
it is just me and the baby,
所以我想我们死定了
so I'm thinking they can take us.
所以我就只好
And so I, uh, heh...
把小孩传到前场
I just heave it downfield.
你疯了不成 那是个婴儿耶
What are you, crazy? That's a baby.
难不成他应该上垒
He should take the sack?
总之突然间我来到前场
Anyway, suddenly I'm downfield.
我发现
And I realize that
该接住孩子的是我 对吧
I'm the one who's supposed to catch him, right?
但我知道我绝对不可能
Only I know theres no way
及时赶到
I'm not gonna get there in time.
所以我就一直跑一直跑
So I am running and I'm running...
然后我就醒来了
and that is when I woke up.
看 我绝对还没准备好去当一个父亲
See I am so not ready to be a father.
你没问题的
Hey,you're gonna be fine.
你是整个北美最细心
You're one of the most caring,
最有责任感的男人
the most responsible men in North America.
你会是好爸爸的
You're gonna make a great dad.
没错 罗斯 你和你儿子只需要更好的阻挡
Yeah, Ross. You and the baby just need better blocking.
对了 你们有谁去过彩虹屋吗?
Oh,have either of you guys ever been to the Rainbow Room?
真有那么贵吗?
Is it real expensive?
除非你要点些什么东西
Only if you order stuff.
我今晚要带乌苏拉去 今天她生日
I'm taking Ursula tonight. It's her birthday.
那菲比生日怎么办
Whoa, what about Phoebe's birthday?
她什么时候生日
When's that?
今晚啊
Tonight.
怎么这么巧
Ugh, man, what are the odds of that happening?
你慢慢想
You take your time.
终于懂了
There it is.
你怎么打算怎么办
So, what are you gonna do?
能怎么办
What can I do?
我不想搞砸和乌苏拉这边的事
Look, I don't want to do anything to screw it up with Ursula.
那你的朋友菲比就可以吗
And your friend Phoebe?
如果她是朋友希望她能谅解
If she is my friend, hopefully she'll understand.
你们不会这样吗
I mean, wouldn't you guys?
老兄 如果是我生日 你给我搞这套
Man, if you tried something like that on my birthday
你就等着看我发飚吧
you'd be staring at the business end of a hissy fit.
加一小撮藏红花 效果会大不同
You add a pinch of saffron, it makes all the difference.
摩妮卡
Okay,uh, Monica?
是
Yes!
对 她是
Yes she is.
你好 这是我朋友瑞秋
Hi! This is my friend Rachel.
你好
Hi!
瑞秋 我是米契尔大夫
Hi, uh, Rachel, I'm Dr. Mitchell.
我是他朋友罗森大夫
And I'm his friend Dr. Rosen.
作为一个大夫 你会不会太帅了点
Aren't you a little cute to be a doctor?
抱歉
Excuse me?
天呀 年轻 我是说年轻
God, young, young. I meant young.
当大夫年轻了点
Young to be a doctor.
说得好 瑞秋
Oh good, Rach.
谢谢      很好
Thank you.        Right.
医生说只是扭到 没什么了
So he said it was just a sprain, and that was it.
你忘了说我们做的蠢事
You left out the stupid part.
才不蠢呢
It's not stupid.
那两个非常非常帅的医生
The very cute cute cute doctors
约我们明晚出去
asked us out for tomorrow night
我答应了
and I said yes.
太疯狂了
I think it's totally insane.
他们可是在那家医院上班
I mean, they work for the hospital.
这简直就像重回犯罪现场一样
It's like returning to the scene of the crime.
我们还是取消约会好了
Y'know, l say we blow off the dates.
啥 摩妮卡
What? Monica
他们可是帅哥 又是医生
they are cute. They are doctors.
帅哥医生 医生帅哥
Cute doctors. Doctors who are cute.
到目前为止我们了解些什么
All right, what have we learned so far?
天啊
Oh, God!
惊喜
Surprise!
你们搞什么啦 吓死我了
What the hell are you doing? You scared the crap out of me.
那是蛋糕吗
Was that the cake?
对 我买了个柠檬烂糕
Yeah, yeah. I got a lemon shmush.
快点 她随时会到
Come on. She'll be here any minute.
但愿没砸烂
I hope it's okay.
生日快乐 菲
Happy Birthday, Peehee.
或许可以用玫瑰写个比字
Maybe we can make a B out of one of those roses.
没错 就用特制蛋糕工具
Yeah,we'll just use our special cake tools.
怎么了
Hey,what's going on?
我们只是
Oh. we just...
惊喜
Surprise!
好棒喔 天啊
This is so great. Oh, my God.
一点也不吓人
This was not at all scary.
各位 蓓蒂
Hi, everybody. Hi, Betty.
蓓蒂
Betty, hi.
你们找来蓓蒂 天啊 好棒
You found Betty. Oh, my gosh. This is so great.
我喜欢的人欢聚一堂
Everybody I love is in the same room.
乔伊呢
Where's Joey?
看到蓓蒂吗
Did you see Betty?
跟你说吧  我不介意
I tell you one thing, I wouldn't mind
投资日晒蕃茄干产业
having a piece of this sundried tomato business.
五年前 要是有人跟我说
Five years ago, if somebody had said to me
我们可以让蕃茄变成西梅干
"Here's a tomato that looks like a prune"
我会说“给我滚出去”
l'd say "Get out of my office."
老爸 我出生前你紧张吗
Dad, before I was born did you freak out at all?
我没紧张 我只是说
I'm not freaking out. I'm just saying..
要是有人来跟我说
if someone had come to me with the idea...
老爸 我是在说关于孩子的事
Dad, Dad, Dad. I'm talking about the whole, baby thing.
你有过那种
Did you, uh, ever get this sort of panicky,
为人父恐慌症吗
"Oh,my God,I'm gonna be a father" kind of a thing?
没有 你妈很尽责
No,your mother really did the work.
我全心冲事业
I was busy with the business.
我不常在家
I wasn't around that much.
你找我来就是为了这个吗
Is that what this is about?
不是啦老爸 我只是在想
No, no, Dad. I was just wondering...
还来得及弥补
There's time to make up for that.
我们可以一起做些事情
We can do stuff together.
你一直说想去威廉斯堡
You always wanted to go to colonial Williamsburg.
要不我们去吧
How about we do that?
谢了 老爸
Thanks, Dad. Really, heh.
我只是
You know, I just, I just...
我只是想弄清楚
I just needed to know, urn...
你是何时才觉得自己已经当了父亲
when did you start to feel like a father?
我想应该是
Oh. Well, I guess it must have been
你出生那天
the day after you were born.
我们在病房里 你妈在睡觉
We were in the hospital room, your mother was asleep
他们把你抱进来交给我
and they brought you in and gave you to me.
你那时还又红又丑又小
You were this ugly little red thing.
突然间
And all of a sudden,
你用拳头抓住了我的手指
you grabbed my finger with your whole fist
紧紧地捏住它
and you squeezed it so tight.
那时候我才感觉到
And that's when I knew.
那你不想去威廉斯堡吗
So you don't want to go to Williamsburg?
可以啊
We can go to Williamsburg.
吃鱼吧
Eat your fish.
瑞秋 帅医生来了
Rachel, the cute doctors are here.
来了
Okay, coming.
请进 麦可 杰夫瑞
Hi, come on in. Hey, Michael, Jeffrey
嗨      嗨
Hi.         Hi.
我们带了酒来
Uh, here, we brought wine.
看看这个 这是波格奈酒庄的名酒
Look at this. It's from the cellars of Ernest and Tova Borgnine.
怎么能不喝
So how could we resist?
太棒了 你看看
Oh,that's great. Look at that.
摩妮卡 你的脚踝怎么样了
So, Monica, how's the ankle?
它呀
lt's,uh...
你自己讲吧
Why don't you tell them?
毕竟脚踝长在你身上
After all, it is your ankle.
感觉好多了 谢谢
You know it's feeling a lot better. Thank you.
你们快请坐
Listen, why don't you guys sit down,
我们去拿杯子
and we'll get you some glasses.
好
Okay
快坐好
STAT
听着 我在想
Okay, listen, I'm thinking
我们为什么不干脆把身份说清楚呢
why don't we just tell them who we really are?
不会有事的 绝对不会有事的
l mean it'll be fine. I really think it will be fine.
不可能 我们会惹上麻烦的
It will not be fine. We'll get in trouble.
摩妮卡 别这么没用好吗
Monica, would you stop being such a wuss?
没用 抱歉 我生活在真实世界中
A wuss? Excuse me for living in the real world, okay?
怎么样
So?
她们看起来很正常
So they still seem normal.
因为她们本来就很正常
That's because they are.
你必须得承认
You have to admit,
我们每次跟在医院认识的人约会都
when we go out with women we meet at the hospital, turns...
放松点 你看看身边
Would you relax? Take a look around.
没有异教徒的圣坛
There are no pagan altars.
角落里没有骨头堆
no piles of bones in the corners.
她们没问题 跟我这样做
They're fine. Go like this:
我们绝不能这样做
I said we are not going to do it, okay?
你有时候真的太天真
Sometimes you can be such a big baby.
我才不天真      认真点
I am not a baby.         Be serious.
是你穷紧张      你有公主病
You get uptight.        You act like a princess.
你知道吗        什么
You know what?      What?
你越来越像你妈
Every day you are becoming more and more like your mother
借过 来了
Excuse me. Hello, here we go.
这地方真不错 你们在这儿住多久了
This is a great place. How long have you lived here?
谢谢 差不多六年
Thanks, I've been here about six years.
瑞秋几个月前才搬来的
And Rachel moved in a few months ago.
我本来要嫁人了
See, I was supposed to get married
但临到圣坛才甩了人家
but, urn, I left the guy at the altar
真的吗      真的
Really?         Yeah.
这是有点自私 不过
Yeah I know its pretty selfish, but
我就是这种人
hey, that's me.
尝尝鹰嘴豆泥吧
Why don't you try the hummus?
摩妮卡 你从事什么工作
So, Monica, what do you do?
我是上流餐厅的大厨
I am a chef at a restaurant uptown.
好厉害      没错
Oh, good for you.         Yeah, it is.
多数是因为我可以到处指使别人
Mostly because I get to boss people around,
而这正好是我的嗜好
which I just love to do.
鹰嘴豆泥很好吃
Well, this hummus is great.
天佑鹰嘴豆
God bless the chickpea.
天啊
Oh, God!
我真是被宠坏了
I am so spoiled.
没了
That's it.
我刚有提过高中时
And by the way, have I mentioned that back in high school
我胖得像猪吗
I was a cow?
我以前会尿床
I used to wet my bed.
我用胸部吸引人的注意
I use my breasts to get other people's attention.
我们都这样
We both do that.
摩妮卡和瑞秋住处
Monica and Rachel's apartment.
等等 瑞秋 是你爸爸
UhUh, yeah, just one second. Uh Rachel, it's your dad.
嗨 老爸
Hi, Dad.
不 是我
No. no. It's me.
爸 现在不方便
Listen, Dad, I can't talk right now. Urn...
有件事
But there's something, urn...
我一直想跟你说
There's something that I've been meaning to tell you.
失陪一下下
Just excuse me for a second.
记得大一时
Remember back in freshman year?
比利德端斯金和我在你们床上做爱
Well, Billy Dreskin and I had sex on your bed.
爸 爸 爸
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy,
怎么可能 我怎么可能会跟比利德瑞斯金上床
Why, why would I sleep with Billy Dreskin?
他爸可是你工作上的死对头
His father tried to put you out of business.
你死定了
You are dead.
罗斯 他又拿到遥控器
Ross, he's got the remote again.
太好了
Good.
或许他能把台转回来
Maybe he can switch it back.
或许不会
Maybe not.
喂
Hello?
是
Uh, ueah... Uh...
好 等等  让我
Okay, uh, hold on a second and let me
让我看看她在不在
let me just check and see if she's here.
是医院入院处的护士
It's the woman from the hospital admissions office.
她说表格有问题
There's a problem with the form.
天啊 怎么办
Oh, God, what do we do?
我不知道 先问清什么事
I don't know. Just find out what they want.
搞清楚他们要什么
Find out what they want
好 不 你来问
Okay. No, you do it.
喂 我是摩妮卡
Hello, this is Monica.
是 噢 好的
Yeah? Oh, okay!
好的 马上过去 谢谢
Yes, we'll be right down. Thank you.
怎么了
what?
有一张入院单忘了签名
We forgot to sign one of the admissions forms.
噢 你说的对 你说的对
Oh! Okay, you were right,you were right,
不值得这样
This was just not worth it.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 我去换衣服
Okay, let me just change.
好
Yes.
好      好
Hey        Hey.
有心事?
Trouble?
你姐姐那晚放我鸽子了
Your sister stood me up the other night.
不是吧
Oh, no.
被人放鸽子的感觉不好受吧
Don't you hate it when people aren't there for you?
有打电话给她吗
Did you try calling her?
我这两天一直在打
I've been trying for two days.
打电话到餐厅
When I called the restaurant
他们说她很忙
they said she was too busy to talk.
我简直不敢相信她想甩了我
I can't believe she's blowing me off.
你好
Hey
噢
Oh
有空吗
Urn, you got a minute?
有啊 就工作 没什么
Urn, yeah, I'm just working.
那       嗯
So         U hhuh?
我带了生日礼物给你
Urn, oh, I got you a birthday present.
你记得喔
Oh, wow, you remembered.
一个茱蒂杰森热水壶
Oh. It's a Judy Jetson Thermos.
是呀 就像你
Right. Like the kind you...
对 对了 我也有东西送给你
Right. Oh, I got something for you too.
你怎么知道我要来
How'd you know I was coming?
我们是双胞胎嘛
Urn, yeah, urn,twin thing.
不敢相信你会这样
I can't believe you did this.
不敢相信你会
I can't believe you
这样
did this.
你和乔伊怎么了
So, what's the deal with, urn, you and Joey?
这个嘛
Oh, right.
他人很好 但我们结束了
He is so great. But that's over.
他知道吗      谁
Does he know?         Who?
乔伊 他对你很着迷
Joey. You know, urn, he's really nutsy about you.
是吗 为什么
He is? Why?
你可把我问倒了
You got me.
没错 劳驾 这不是应该有配沙拉的吗?
Right. Excuse me, doesn't this come with a side salad?
你会打电话给他吗
So, urn, are you gonna call him?
你认为他喜欢我吗
What, you think he likes me?
不是他 是乔伊
No. Joey.
不会 他很聪明 他自己会想明白的
Oh, no, no. He is so smart. He'll figure it out.
要吃鸡肉吗
Do you want some chicken?
不了 有脸的东西不吃 记得吗
No, no, no food with a face, remember?
你一点儿没变
You have not changed.
是 你也一样
Yeah, you too.
你好 记得我们吗
Hi! Remember us?
你之前打电话来
Urn, yeah, you just called a little while ago
说入院表格要签名
about needing a signature on the admissions form?
看来我们需要一张全新的表格
Well, it turns out we need a whole new one.
因为呢
Because, urn, you see...
名字又写错了
I put the wrong name again.
因为      你就是这么笨
Because...        You're that stupid.
没错 我就是这么笨
I am. I'm that stupid.
我用支票支付吧
Yeah, and I'm just gonna pay for this with a check.
你知道你的保险是可以付的吧
You know, your insurance will cover that.
知道 只是我也不怎么聪明
Yeah I know. I'm just not that bright either.
好吧 最差的状况是
Okay, worst case scenario:
如果说你从来不觉得自己像个父亲
Say you never feel like a father.
嗯
Uhhuh.
你的儿子从没觉得你是他父亲
Say your son never feels connected to you as one.
他所有的人际关系全部受此影响
Say all of his relationships are affected by this.
你讲的话有重点吗
Do you have a point?
应该有的
You know,you'd think I would.
猴子是怎么了
What's up with the simian?
只是个毛球
It's just a fur ball.
好吧 该谁了
Okay, whose turn is it?
该你了 我拼出了"KIDNEY" 得43分
Yours. I just got 43 points for "KIENEY".
不 你没得分 你拼的是"IDNEY"
No, you got zero points for "IDNEY".
我有个"K"的 "K"呢
I had a "K". Where's my "K"?
快帮帮我 我的猴子吞了一颗K
You've got to help me. My monkey swallowed a "K".
那把东西给我抱出去
You had to get that animal out of here.
不 你不了解
No, you don't understand.
动物医院在城的另一边
The animal hospital is way across town.
他噎到了 我不知如何是好
He's choking. I don't know what else to do.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
马塞尔把一个拼字牌吞下去了
Marcel swallowed a Scrabble tile.
对不起 这个医院是医人的
Excuse me. This hospital is for people.
护士 他是人 他有名字
Lady, he is people. He has a name, okay?
他还会看电视
He watches Jeopardy...
没人注意时还会摸自己
he touches himself when nobody's watching.
求求你发发善心
Please, please, have a heart.
我来看看吧
I'll take a look at him.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
麦可      瑞秋
Michael         Rachel
什么      摩妮卡
What?         Monica.
噢       嗨
Oh!         Hi!
嘿
Hey.
乌苏拉
Urs.
你怎么会来这儿 我一直打电话找你
What are you doing here? I've been trying to call you.
听我说
Listen, urn...
别 别 别让我听
No, no, don't say "listen".
我认得这个听 我也用过
I know that "listen". I've said that "listen".
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我实在是不懂  到底怎么了
I don't get it. What happened?
你在桥下说的那些话呢
What about everything you said under the bridge?
对
Yeah, urn, ahem.
你还是忘了我在桥下说的话吧
You know,you should just forget about what I said under the bridge.
那晚我太醉了全是胡说
I was talking crazy that night. I was so drunk.
你不喝酒的
You don't drink.
没错 我不喝酒
That's right, I don't.
但是我是因你而醉
But I was drunk on you.
乌苏拉
Oh Urs.
但我们不可能有进展的
Okay, yeah, so it's not gonna work.
为什么 是因为我是菲比的朋友
Why? Is it because I'm friends with Phoebe?
如果是这个原因 你会愿意跟她绝交吗
If it was, would you stop hanging out with her?
不行 我办不到
No, no, I couldn't do that.
那没错 就是因为菲比
Urn, then, yeah, it's 'cause of Phoebe.
我跟她只能选一个
So, you know, it's either her or me.
那么我只能说抱歉了
Then, uh... Then I'm sorry.
忘掉你是件很难的事
You know, you're gonna be really, really hard to get over.
我知道
I know.
不知道是因为要分手还是
I don't know whether it's just because were breaking up or what...
但你从没这么美过
but you have never looked so beautiful.
真的吗
Really?
菲比
Pheebs?
什么事
Yeah.
他看起来好小
He looks so tiny.
我们收到消息了      他没事吧
We just got the message.        Is he all right?
医生把"K"拿出来了
Yeah, the doctor got the "K" out.
他还找到一个"M"和一个"O"
He also found an "M" and an "O".
我们猜他是想拼 “MONKEY”（猴子）
We think he was trying to spell out "MONKEY".
医生说他没事了
The doctor says he's gonna be fine.
他现在只是睡着了
He's just sleeping now.
你现在有当父亲的感觉了吗
So you feel like a dad yet?
没有 怎么了
No. Why?
你都撑过来了
Hey, come on, you came through.
做了该做的事
You did what you had to do.
很有当爸的样子
That is very dad.
快看 他醒了
Oh, look, he's waking up.
老兄 你怎么样
Hey, fella. How you doing?
海盗编号：HDT17-P1-24-17-01-1212
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧